0

You have 0 items in your cart

Go To Shopping

0

You have 0 items in your cart

Go To Shopping

Privacy Policy
==============

Young Americans for Liberty, Inc. (YAL) and/or Young Americans for Liberty Foundation (YALF) (collectively, “we”, “us” or “our”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our websites about how we collect, use, and maintain information we collect or may collect about them. “Website(s)” or “Sites” includes the YAL worldwide web location, any subpages or mobile-optimized versions of other websites operated by YAL or YALF, whether or not explicitly stated. Your use of our website(s) is governed by this Privacy Policy and our [Terms and Conditions](https://yaliberty.org/terms-and-conditions/). This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect when you visit our website(s), how we use that information, and what choices you have about how it is used. Use of our website(s) constitutes acceptance of all terms contained herein. 

### **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

When you visit our website, we may collect certain personal identifying information (PII) from you, including, without limitation, your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, and other contact information. Certain actions and areas on our Sites require providing of PII, including, without limitation;

* Making a donation
* Taking action to contact a public official
* Signing a petition
* Registration or applications for an event or conference
* Making a purchase through our online store
* Volunteer opportunities
* Job opportunities and applications
* Recommending candidates for the Hazlitt Coalition

We may also collect PII about your usage of our website, such as your IP address, browser type, and operating system, and other information associated with your PII such as interests, preferences, and demographics.

YAL and its affiliates control and make available its websites from its facilities in the United States of America. Those who access this website from outside the United States from other jurisdictions do so at their own risk and are solely responsible for compliance with their local laws. Information may be stored within the United States or elsewhere in YAL’s sole discretion.

### **Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

We may use PII and other information we collect about you for purposes described in this policy or disclosed to you on our website(s) or in connection with our services. This includes, without limitation:

1. Operating and improving our website(s), products and services;
2. Responding to your inquiries, comments, questions, or requests;
3. Communicating with you about our services, promotions, and events
4. Personalizing your experience using our website(s), products and services;
5. Analyzing and monitoring usage of our website(s)
6. Compliance with legal obligations or investigations into illegal, fraudulent, or improper activity.

We may disclose your personal information to third-party service providers who assist us in providing our services, such as hosting providers, payment processors, and analytics providers. We may also disclose your personal information if required by law or to protect our legal rights.

**Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share your PII for the following purposes and under the following circumstances:

1. We may share your PII with our affiliates, including affiliated organizations, technical consultants, auditors and other third parties who act on our behalf, for example, to make our website(s) available, enhance their functionality, or provide associated services, and/or who deal with you in delivering content, samples, products, and gifts and prizes.
2. We may share or transfer certain PII we collect through our website(s), along with certain other information about you, to similarly situated like-minded organizations for similar purposes to our own.
3. We may transfer your personally identifiable information and other information in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture or disclosure of all or a portion of our assets to another party.
4. We may release, in our sole discretion, personal information to third parties: to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of YAL, our agents, customers, members, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of our employees, customers, or any person.

We may also provide aggregate statistics and de-identified data about our customers, including traffic patterns and related site information, to third parties for their own purposes, including statistical analysis.

If you do not wish to receive promotional and newsletter emails from us, you may click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email. If you opt-out of promotional or newsletter emails from us, we may continue to send you certain communications such as service announcements and administrative messages that relate to us and our website(s) that are necessary to our relationship with you. For all other requests for changes relating to your PII, including opting out of email and our sharing PII with our partners, please contact us at contact@yaliberty.org.‬

### **Your Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

Please be aware when you connect and share your actions, comments, content and information, for example, through discussion board postings on our website(s), those actions are not private. Others may capture personal information you post, including your email address, and may use the data to identify or contact you, including to send you emails. We cannot control such actions by others. Please be mindful of your own privacy needs as you choose whom to connect with and what to share and make public. If you share information about others, please be sure to respect their privacy and get consent for any information you may share about them.

### **Third Party Activities**

If you submit or chose to share PII through a form or posting on any page of our website(s), choose to otherwise share your PII with a third party such as by connecting with social networking services, or click on a link on our website(s) to go to a third-party site that may collect information about you, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of, including any marketing or other use of your PII by, those third parties. To learn more about any other company or organization’s privacy practices, we suggest you contact them directly about their privacy policy.

### **Do Not Track Disclosures**

We do not respond to Do Not Track signals sent by various web browsers. To date, a clear standard has yet to be developed concerning these signals and how they should be treated by website operators. Thus, we do not respond to any Do Not Track signals sent by an individual user’s web browser. We are permitted pursuant to this Privacy Policy to share any information you provide through use of our website(s) with third parties. If you do not wish to consent to the provision of your PII in this manner, you should stop using our website(s) immediately and contact us at contact@yaliberty.org to be removed from our database.

### **Third Party Advertising**

We may also use third parties to collect information about our website visitors or to serve ads on our website(s). Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our website(s) (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this by using cookies, clear gifs, or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our website(s) and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

You may opt-out of interest-based advertising by visiting [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/). Please note that this will only allow you to opt-out of tailored advertisements delivered by members of NAI and that we are not associated with or responsible for the management and processing of these requests.

### **Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect information about how our website is used, your usage of our website, and to personalize your experience. Your web browser may provide you with the ability to accept or decline cookies. If you decline cookies, some features of our website may be limited or not be available to you.

### **Company Ads on Third Party Sites**

We may use information collected using third party cookies and Web beacons on our website(s) and in our emails to deliver advertising displayed to you on third party sites. We also may use cookie information to know when you return to our website(s) after visiting these third-party sites. We use this information and other information about you to try to understand your interests and show you relevant advertising about products and services you may be interested in.

**Web Beacons and Server Logs**

We, or a third party, may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on Company Sites or in our emails. We and these third parties use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. These third parties have their own privacy policies that govern the use of the data collected, which may be different from this Privacy Policy.

Server logs capture certain non-personally identifying data, such as the time and date of a Web visit, the browser and operating system being used, and the Web URL a user linked from. This information is used in aggregate form to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content that is compatible with our visitors’ Web-browsing systems. We also collect information about keyword searches performed by visitors on our website(s). We may keep logs of all words searched to help us learn what kinds of information our website(s) visitors are seeking, and to improve our service to visitors.

### **Security & Privacy**

We take commercially reasonable measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, and use. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, including through web pages or e-mail, is 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. If you are concerned about any communication with us being intercepted, please consider contacting us via other means.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our website is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

### **Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy along with our Terms and Conditions periodically.

**Terms and Conditions**

**Please read these Terms and Con****ditions of use carefully before using this site or engaging with Young Americans for Liberty Foundation and/or Young Americans for Liberty, Inc.**
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This Terms and Conditions is applicable to Young Americans for Liberty Foundation and/or Young Americans for Liberty Inc. and any of its websites, domains, subpages, mobile sites, mobile applications, and/or online accounts owned, and operated, maintained, or controlled by Young Americans for Liberty Foundation and/or Young Americans for Liberty Inc., and worldwide web location and mobile-optimized versions of the same (collectively “YAL”, “we”, “us” or “our”). Your use of YAL is governed by these Terms and Conditions and our [Privacy Policy](https://yaliberty.org/privacy-policy/). Use of YAL’s website constitutes acceptance of all terms contained herein. If you do not accept any of the terms contained herein, you must cease use of YAL’s website immediately.

We may revise and update these Terms and Conditions at any time, with or without notice. Your continued usage of YAL’s website will mean you accept those changes. 

### **Text Messaging**

By affirmatively indicating “Yes” when asked whether you would like to receive text messages from YAL, you are providing your express written consent to receive text messages from us using automated and/or peer-to-peer technology. You further affirm that, by providing such consent that you are at least 18 years of age or older and have the authority to grant such consent. Your mobile service provider may charge standard messaging, data, and other rates/fees related to any text transmissions. You may opt out at any time and for any reason. 

As we have no control over how the mobile service providers transmit our text messages, we cannot be responsible or liable for any delays in your receipt of any of our text messages. We make no warranty, express or implied, and all warranties, including implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose are expressly disclaimed. Our text messages are provided on an “as is” basis.

By opting-in to our text messages, you recognize we may collect certain data from you. Such data may include, but is not limited to, your mobile phone number, your mobile service provider’s name, and the date, time, and content of your messages to and from us, along with any other. You expressly agree that, in the event you forfeit or no longer utilize the cellular telephone number you used to subscribe to our text messaging campaign, you will immediately notify us of this change.

### **Dispute Resolution and Arbitration**

Except for temporary, preliminary, or permanent injunctive relief or any form of equitable relief as deemed necessary by us in our sole discretion, all disputes arising from or relating to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy and the activities described herein, including those claims which may arise after the relationship between us allegedly terminates, shall be submitted to a single arbitrator for binding arbitration under proceedings conducted in accordance with the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) then in effect. You further recognize and expressly agree that all claims related to these Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, and the activities specified herein shall proceed on an individual (non-class and non-representative) basis, that the presiding arbitrator is limited to awarding relief on an individual (non-class and non-representative) basis, and that the arbitration proceedings and any specified award shall remain confidential, except where disclosure may be necessary in connection with a court application for a preliminary injunction, judicial challenge to an award or enforcement thereof, or otherwise required by law or judicial decision. You acknowledge that by agreeing to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, you hereby knowingly and voluntarily waive any right you have to a jury trial, or an appeal to a state or federal court of appeal, concerning any dispute that may arise pursuant to this Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE ALL DISPUTES ARISING THERETO SHALL BE RESOLVED THROUGH BINDING ARBITRATION AND NO CLASS ACTION, CONSOLIDATED ACTION, PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL, OR OTHER REPRESENTATIVE CLAIMS MAY BE PURSUED IN ARBITRATION. You further affirmatively waive your right to initiate and/or participate in any such proceedings as contemplated by this Dispute Resolution and Arbitration provision.

### **Governing Law**

These Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, including the use of information (including personally identifiable information) provided or accessible through YAL, are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas without regard to its conflict of laws principles. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to these Terms and Conditions or your use of this site shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the State of Texas.

### **Indemnity**

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless us, our affiliates, clients, licensors and suppliers, and the directors, officers, employees, agents, licensees, representatives and independent contractors of the foregoing from and against any claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements including without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your violation of these Terms and Conditions, your submissions to YAL, your violation of any rights of another or applicable laws and regulations, or your use of any content on or accessible through YAL. 

### **Use of Content**

YAL and any and all content on or available throughout YAL’s website and linked social media pages, including without limitation, text, graphics, images, software, audio, video, information, data materials, products, and services (collectively, the “Content”) is owned by us or our content providers. Subject to these Terms and Conditions, the Content is protected by copyright under both United States and foreign laws and international treaties. Any use of the Content not expressly permitted by these Terms and Conditions is a breach of these Terms and Conditions and may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws or the rights of third parties. Content and features are subject to change or termination without notice at our sole and exclusive editorial discretion. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved to us. If you violate any of these Terms of Service, your permission to use the Content automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any copies you have made of any portion of the Content.

### **Limitation on Liability**

When using YAL’s website, information may be transmitted using a medium and/or jurisdiction beyond our control and jurisdiction and that of our suppliers. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any delay, failure, interruption or corruption of any data or other information transmitted in connection with use of YAL.

YAL and the Content are provided on an “AS IS” basis. WE AND OUR AFFILIATES, CLIENTS, LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTIES’ RIGHTS, AND FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WE, OUR AFFILIATES, CLIENTS, LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS ALSO MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO WHETHER THE INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA YAL’s WEBSITE, OR ANY WEB SITE WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED, IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE, TRUTHFUL OR CURRENT. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy and completeness of all information, opinions, and other material on our website or any website with which it is linked. Price information and promotions are subject to change without notice. Without limiting the foregoing, we and our affiliates, clients, licensors and suppliers make no representations or warranties about the following:

1. The software, text, graphics, links, or communications provided on or through the use of YAL’s website or related material from us.
2. The satisfaction of any government regulations requiring disclosure of information on any products (e.g. prescription drugs) with regard to the Content contained on YAL’s website.

In no event shall we, our affiliates, clients, licensors, suppliers, or any third parties mentioned on YAL’s website be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, incidental and consequential damages, personal injury/wrongful death, lost profits, or damages resulting from lost data or business interruption) resulting from the use or inability to use YAL’s website or the Content, or damage to your computer system due to viruses or other defects, whether based on warranty, contract, tort or any other legal theory, whether or not we advise you of the possibility of such damages. We are not liable for any personal injury, including death, caused by your use or misuse of YAL’s website or content or for any other breach by you of these Terms and Conditions. Any claims arising in connection with your use of YAL’s website must be brought within one (1) year of the date of the event giving rise to such action occurred, regardless of when such event becomes known. Any action not brought within one year from the date of the triggering event shall be barred, without regard to any other statute of limitations established by law. Your remedies under these Terms and Conditions are exclusive and are limited to those expressly provided for in these Terms and Conditions.

You understand and agree that your use of our website(s) creates no partnership, employment relationship, agency of any kind, or any other legal relationship between you and YAL. This includes, without limitation, submission of content to our Site(s), registration for events, application for jobs posted on the Site(s), application for or acceptance of volunteer positions, and agreement to receive communications.

### **User Submissions**

By voluntarily submitting any information, communications, or content (including, but not limited to, photos, videos, personal stories, anecdotes, and jokes) (each a “Submitted Item”) to this Site(s), you agree such submissions are non-confidential for all purposes and you grant us and our affiliates, partners, and clients worldwide an irrevocable, nonexclusive, perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, fully sub-licensable, right and license to use, display, publicly perform, modify, reproduce, publish, distribute, adapt, make derivative works of, sublicense and otherwise commercially and non-commercially exploit your Submitted Items and all copyright, trade secret, trademark or other intellectual property rights therein, in any manner or medium now existing or hereafter developed (including but not limited to print, film or electronic storage devices), without compensation of any kind to you or any third party, and the right to include your name and city of residence in connection with any such use. Each Submitted Item is also subject to such other terms and conditions as any of the affiliates, partners, and clients may specify for particular submissions. By submitting material to us or our affiliates, partners, and clients, you represent and warrant you have full authority to grant the rights set forth above and your material will not, in whole or in part, infringe the intellectual property rights, rights of privacy or publicity, or any other rights of any third party. You further represent and warrant you have attained the legal age of majority in your state/province (18 in most states/provinces). A parent or guardian must submit on behalf of any minor. The submission of any Submitted Item in no way creates any obligation or duty on our part or the part of any affiliate, partner, or client to post or use such Submitted Item or to give you credit. We may contact you via phone, email or mail regarding your submission.

### **Children’s Privacy**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. YAL’s website is not intended or designed to attract children younger than 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is a child younger than 13. To further learn about our privacy commitment, please refer to the [Privacy Policy](https://yaliberty.org/privacy-policy/).

### **DMCA Notice and Customer Care**

YAL does not permit activities that infringe on the copyrights and intellectual property rights of others. You agree you will not upload or transmit any communications or content of any type that infringe or violate any rights of any party. You should notify us promptly if you believe any materials on YAL’s website, including advertisements, or materials available on or through links, frames, indexes and directories linked to YAL, infringe a third-party copyright. Upon our receipt of a proper notice of claimed infringement under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the “DMCA”), we will respond expeditiously to remove, or disable access to, the material claimed to be infringing and will follow the procedures specified in the DMCA to resolve the claim between the notifying party and the alleged infringer who provided the content at issue.

To provide notice of claimed copyright infringement:  
Young Americans for Liberty

ATTN: General Counsel

3267 Bee Caves Road  
Ste 107-65  
Austin, Texas 78746

VIA E-MAIL: [contact@yaliberty.org](mailto:contact@yaliberty.org) (must include DMCA Notice ATTN: General Counsel in subject line)

It is our policy to terminate contractual relationships regarding content with third parties who repeatedly infringe the copyrights of others.

### **Site Usage**

You agree to use this Site and any other site governed by these terms and conditions in accordance with the below policies. If you cannot comply with these policies, cease use of our websites immediately.

1. Content is provided “AS IS.” You are solely responsible for your reliance on and use of such content. If you feel threatened or believe someone else is in danger, you should take appropriate action such as contacting your local law enforcement agency immediately. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.
2. You must be 18 years or older.
3. The information you submit through any of our Site(s) will not be considered confidential and may be publicly available to third parties. You agree not to reveal any private information, including but not limited to health, financial and personally identifiable information, if you do not wish this information to be published. Furthermore, you agree not to reveal the health or other private information of third parties without their knowledge and consent.
4. You agree not to upload to or distribute or otherwise publish any content that is libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, slanderous, threatening, harassing, or abusive, to any other person or entity, or is otherwise inappropriate or unlawful. You are solely responsible for the content of the messages you post. Any post that is removed by us is done at our sole discretion and may not be appealed.
5. You may not use our Site(s) for any purpose in violation of local, state, or federal laws or regulations.
6. You agree not to upload to or distribute or otherwise publish any content that violates or infringes the copyright, trademark, or any other personal or proprietary rights of any third party.
7. Messages, information, or other materials posted by you on our Site(s) are subject to use by us and our licensees in any medium (now in existence or hereafter developed), for any purpose, in perpetuity without further notice or any compensation of any kind to you or any third party. The submission of such materials in no way creates any obligation or duty on our part to post or use such materials, or to give you any credit.
8. You agree not to, without our express approval, distribute or otherwise publish any material containing any solicitation of funds, advertising or solicitation for goods or services for any business purpose.
9. You agree not to disrupt the normal flow of dialogue, or post comments not related to the topic being discussed (unless it is clear the discussion is free form), or otherwise engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying the Site, or which, in our sole judgment, exposes us or any of our affiliates, clients, licensors, licensees, or suppliers to any liability or detriment of any type.
10. You agree not to post chain letters or pyramid schemes; impersonate another person or allow another person or entity to use your identification for posting or viewing comments; distribute viruses or other harmful computer code; harvest or otherwise collect information about others (including email addresses) without their consent; or post the same note more than once or “spam.”
11. If you become aware of a violation of these policies, please notify us by sending a detailed email message to [contact@yaliberty.org](mailto:contact@yaliberty.org). If you are writing to report a copyright infringement, please follow the procedure set forth in the section entitled “DMCA Notice” in these Terms of Service.

We reserve the right (but are not obligated) to do any or all of the following:

1. Investigate any allegation a communication(s) does not conform to these Terms and Conditions and determine in its sole discretion to remove or request the removal of the communication(s).
2. Terminate a user’s access upon any breach of the Terms and Conditions.
3. Monitor, disclose, delete, move or edit communications determined, in our sole discretion, to be abusive, defamatory, obscene, in violation of copyright or trademark laws, otherwise illegal, disruptive, or otherwise unacceptable for any reason or no reason in our sole discretion regardless of whether the communication violates the Terms & Conditions.

We reserve the right to take any action we deem necessary to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. We have no liability or responsibility to users of our Site(s) or any other person or entity for performance or nonperformance of the aforementioned activities.

### **Advertisements and Links to Other Sites**

Our websites may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by others. We do not endorse the content on any third-party websites. We are not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites, indexes or directories, sites framed within this Site, or third-party advertisements, and do not make any representations regarding their content, accuracy or non-infringement. We do not endorse any product advertised on YAL. Your use of third-party websites is at your own risk and subject to the terms of use of use for such sites. You should be aware both the terms of use and the privacy policies of linked sites may differ from ours.

### **Trademarks**

The tradenames, logos, titles, designs and trademarks under which we and our affiliates, clients, or licensors operate are trademarks of us, our affiliates, clients or licensors and are all proprietary to their respective owners. The trademarks appearing on our Sites are owned either by (1) Young Americans for Liberty (including but not limited to YOUNG AMERICANS FOR LIBERTY and AMERICAN ACTION FUND) or (2) their respective trademark owners. The names of actual companies and products mentioned may be the trademarks of their respective owners. Except as may be specifically permitted in accordance with these Terms and Conditions, any use of such names, tradenames, logos, titles, designs and trademarks is strictly prohibited without the prior written consent of their respective owners. All rights are reserved.

### **General**

If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms and Conditions, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms and Conditions shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition. The following provisions survive the expiration or termination of these Terms and Conditions for any reason whatsoever: Arbitration, Limitation on Liability, User Submissions, Indemnity, General, Jurisdiction, and Complete Agreement.

We are based in the United States of America. We make no claim the Content is appropriate or may be downloaded outside of the United States. Access to and contact or input to the Content may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access YAL from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction. 

### **Complete Agreement**

Except as expressly provided in a particular “legal notice” on the Site, these Terms of Service and our [Privacy Policy](https://yaliberty.org/privacy-policy/) constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to the use of YAL’s website and Content. If you have questions or comments regarding this Site, please contact us at contact@yaliberty.org.
